Mission statement
Pool ideas from each - what to include on site
Bios of each - update/professional 
Google - sign up; adverts  (key words)
Google checkout
Logo - window with four panes
Email Scott about web hosting
Expiration date: March 6, 2009
Sky Asylum.net, org, Sky-Asylum.com
Eric to research Godaddy.com
Dreamhost - 3 years commitment/$8.00




"Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis nostrud exercitation ullamco laboris nisi ut aliquip ex ea commodo consequat. Duis aute irure dolor in reprehenderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sint occaecat cupidatat non proident, sunt in culpa qui officia deserunt mollit anim id est laborum." 